{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855315505","data":{"timestamp":" 947855315505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855327508","data":{"timestamp":" 947855327507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 9d666e16-27a8-4ac5-8058-0b75b9f79e1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855327742","data":{"timestamp":" 947855327741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 9d666e16-27a8-4ac5-8058-0b75b9f79e1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855328720","data":{"timestamp":" 947855328719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 9d666e16-27a8-4ac5-8058-0b75b9f79e1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855330009","data":{"timestamp":" 947855330007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 9d666e16-27a8-4ac5-8058-0b75b9f79e1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855332960","data":{"timestamp":" 947855332959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 9d666e16-27a8-4ac5-8058-0b75b9f79e1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855333726","data":{"timestamp":" 947855333726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 9d666e16-27a8-4ac5-8058-0b75b9f79e1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855333801","data":{"timestamp":" 947855333801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 9d666e16-27a8-4ac5-8058-0b75b9f79e1c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855368939","data":{"timestamp":" 947855368939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855373116","data":{"timestamp":" 947855373116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855382281","data":{"timestamp":" 947855382281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855393179","data":{"timestamp":" 947855393179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855395187","data":{"timestamp":" 947855395187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855405739","data":{"timestamp":" 947855405739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855407469","data":{"timestamp":" 947855407469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855415639","data":{"timestamp":" 947855415639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855427495","data":{"timestamp":" 947855427495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855429617","data":{"timestamp":" 947855429617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855440101","data":{"timestamp":" 947855440101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855441680","data":{"timestamp":" 947855441680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855451830","data":{"timestamp":" 947855451830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855453482","data":{"timestamp":" 947855453482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855461518","data":{"timestamp":" 947855461518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855472991","data":{"timestamp":" 947855472991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855474667","data":{"timestamp":" 947855474667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855484235","data":{"timestamp":" 947855484235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855486515","data":{"timestamp":" 947855486515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855496188","data":{"timestamp":" 947855496188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855498001","data":{"timestamp":" 947855498000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855507333","data":{"timestamp":" 947855507333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855508990","data":{"timestamp":" 947855508990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855524170","data":{"timestamp":" 947855524170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855526563","data":{"timestamp":" 947855526563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855537632","data":{"timestamp":" 947855537631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" dad25f9e-2d5d-4246-8084-f1fee74c0872"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855550329","data":{"timestamp":" 947855550329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_160739"," gameId":" 7f93af07-fca8-4f02-979f-08dbfd63c113"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}